Infants and Kids Oral Hygiene and Care
Exactly what questions mamas get during this particular time?
How do we select right toothbrush?
Which are the types available in the market?
How do we select right toothpaste?
How much to use?
When to use?
How much time we should be using?
What should be the storage type of each of these items?
Does tongue needs to be cleaned?
Is there any specific care that mama needs to take
so that their permanent teeth are not affected?
These are all questions that every new parent have.
In this particular course, you will get tremendous clarity about
toothbrushes, toothpaste, oral hygiene, oral care,
how, when, why, what are the techniques, what are the positions and all of this.
All of you please note,
kids' oral hygiene determines their chewing habits for rest of their life
because habits are formed in the initial years of child's life.
This is going to ensure child's proper brain development.
At the same time, right chewing habits and right oral care
will ensure child's proper speech development.
All of you know, once we take care of Uttar Pradesh of child's body,
Madhya Pradesh is taken care of.
So we have to take care of this opening.
let's go ahead into the course to understand details of each of this topic from an expert
who is a master pediatric dentist let's go ahead into the course